

PETRA KOLARIČ

ABOUT ME

Open for #NewChallenge

Based on past working experience, I am aware of priorities that have to be completed in a timely manner. I am respectful, reliable, confident, and communicative. Task-oriented, team player, and great at finding convenient solutions. Always with a positive attitude, adaptable to implement various tasks.

+386 31 308 812

Slovenia, Europe

www.petrakolaric.com

REFERENCES

PRODUCT MANAGER (MPG) VOLUNTEER (NGO Andromeda)

INTERESTS

COLORS, MARKETING, TECH, UX DESIGN (FASHION, GRAPHIC, WEB)

LANGUAGES

SLOVENE			
ENGLISH			
CROATIAN			
ITALIAN			
GERMAN	ı	ı	

EDUCATION

BA Fashion Designer Faculty of design / Ljubljana, Slovenia

EXPERIENCE

WEBSITE EDITOR 12/2020 - present 10DX GROUP Ltd. / Maribor, Slovenia

Marketing agency 10DX GROUP Ltd. specializes in e-commerce and performance digital marketing. Present on EU and US markets.

Managing product entries and product descriptions, control of

orderliness of websites, proofreading, timeliness of information, price list control, checking the accuracy of stocks, communication with customers and suppliers, tracking delivery deadline, coordination of offers. Close cooperation with marketing and warehouse.

PRODUCT MANAGER 12/2016 - 12/2019 Michael Pachleitner Group / Graz, Austria

Optics company with headquarters in Graz. Design and trading of an extensive range of frame brands, sunglasses, eyeglass lenses, and jewelry designed in Austria.

- Market and competition research, tracking and forecasting fashion trends. Collecting relevant ideas, color combinations, materials, and selecting suppliers for future collections.
- Preparation of technical packages, sending inquiries, offers, orders, and taking into account delivery deadlines.
- Organization, coordination of meetings and participation in business trips, visiting suppliers abroad, optical and fashion fairs.

ART EVENT MANAGER Igrajmo se IC / Ptuj, Slovenia

10/2010 - 11/2016

Organization of cultural events in a fast-paced work environment.

- Involved and worked in creative workshops, fashion shows, outdoor events, musical and theater performances, promotions, team building activities, conferences, weddings, etc.
- Worked as a student and in March 2016, became a full-time employee. Involved in the entire event planning process, preparing and implementing cultural events from inquiry to realization.

ASSISTANT OF BRAND MANAGER EUROPA 92 Ltd. / Zagreb, Croatia

8/2015 - 2/2016

The largest Jeans clothing retailer in Croatia.

- Worked in the design department, providing statistics and documentation to other departments.
- Providing reports technical drawings and packages, preparing materials, mood boards and colors (Adobe Illustrator, Corel Draw).
- Product management up to the last step in the production and control of the collection in actual shops.

SKILLS

MICROSOFT OFFICE SUITE

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR & PHOTOSHOP

ERP SYSTEM (SAP)

WORDPRESS, SHOPIFY

COPYWRITING